http://www.investintech.com/about/legal/termsuse/

Terms of Service
Welcome to the Investintech.com Inc. Web site (the "Site"). By using the Site, you agree to follow and be bound by the following terms and conditions concerning your use of the Site ("Terms of Use") and our Privacy Policy. We may revise the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you.
Use of Web Site Information
Disclaimer
Use of Software
Limitation of Liability
Use of Forums and Public Communication
Indemnity
Passwords and Security
Privacy Policy
Termination of Use
Applicable Laws
Third Party Web Sites, Content, Products and Services
Copyright/Trademark Information
1. Use of Web Site Information
You may download, view, copy and print documents and graphics incorporated in these documents (the "Documents") from the Site subject to the following: (a) the Documents may be used solely for personal, informational, non-commercial purposes; and (b) the Documents may not be modified or altered in any way. Except where your use constitutes "fair use" under copyright law, you may not otherwise use, download, upload, copy, print, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, post, transmit or distribute any information from this Web site in whole or in part without the express authorization of Investintech.com Inc.
2. Use of Software
Any use of software and accompanying documentation you download from the Site is subject to the terms of a software license agreement between you and Investintech.com Inc. You must read the license agreement and indicate your agreement to its terms prior to installing or using the software. All rights, title and interest not expressly granted are reserved.
3. Use of Forums and Public Communication
"Forum" means a discussion group, chat area, bulletin board, news group, letter to Investintech.com Inc., its webmaster or employees, or e-mail function offered as part of the Site. You agree not to upload, email, post, publish or otherwise transmit through a Forum any content that: (a) is false or misleading; (b) is defamatory; (c) is harassing or invades another's privacy, or promotes bigotry, racism, hatred or harm against any group or individual; (d) is obscene; (e) infringes another's rights, including but not limited to intellectual property rights; (f) constitutes unsolicited bulk e-mail, "junk mail," "spam" or chain letters; or (g) violates any applicable laws or regulations. Forums shall be used in a noncommercial manner only. You shall not distribute or otherwise publish any content containing a solicitation of funds, promotion, advertising, solicitation for goods or services, or other commercial matter. You agree not to solicit other users of the Site to use or join or become of any commercial online or offline service or other organization. Except where expressly authorized by Investintech.com Inc., you agree not to collect or store personal data about other users. By uploading, emailing, posting, publishing or otherwise transmitting content to any Forum or submitting any content to Investintech.com Inc., you automatically grant (or warrant that the owner of such rights has expressly granted) Investintech.com Inc. a perpetual, royalty-free, irrevocable, nonexclusive right and license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, transmit and distribute such content on in any form, medium, or technology now known or later developed. In addition, you warrant that all so-called moral rights in the content have been waived.
4. Passwords and Security
You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any password(s) you are given to access the Site, and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password(s). You agree to notify Investintech.com Inc. immediately of any authorized use of your password(s).
5. Termination of Use
You agree that Investintech.com Inc. may, in its sole discretion, at any time terminate your access to the Site and any account(s) you may have in connection with the Site. Access to the Site may be monitored by Investintech.com Inc.
6. Third Party Web Sites, Content, Products and Services
The Site may provide links to Web sites and access to content, products and services from third parties, including users, advertisers, affiliates and sponsors of the Site. You agree that Investintech.com Inc. is not responsible for the availability of, and content provided on, third party Web sites. You should refer to the policies posted by other Web sites regarding privacy and other topics before you use them. You agree that Investintech.com Inc. is not responsible for third party content accessible through the Site, including opinions, advice, statements and advertisements, and understand that you bear all risks associated with the use of such content. If you choose to purchase any products or services from a third party, your relationship is directly with the third party. You agree that Investintech.com Inc. is not responsible for: (a) the quality of third party products or services; and (b) fulfilling any of the terms of your agreement with the seller, including delivery of products or services and warranty obligations related to purchased products or services. You agree that Investintech.com Inc. is not responsible for any loss or damage of any sort you may incur from dealing with any third party.
7. Disclaimer
EXCEPT WHERE EXPRESSLY PROVIDED OTHERWISE, THE SITE, AND ALL CONTENT, MATERIALS, INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS AND SERVICES PROVIDED ON THE SITE, ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS. INVESTINTECH.COM INC. EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. INVESTINTECH.COM INC. MAKES NO WARRANTY THAT: (A) THE SITE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS; (B) THE SITE WILL BE AVAILABLE ON AN UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, OR ERROR-FREE BASIS; (C) THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF THE SITE OR ANY SERVICES OFFERED THROUGH THE SITE WILL BE ACCURATE OR RELIABLE; OR (D) THE QUALITY OF ANY PRODUCTS, SERVICES, INFORMATION, OR OTHER MATERIAL PURCHASED OR OBTAINED BY YOU THROUGH THE SITE WILL MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS. ANY CONTENT, MATERIALS, INFORMATION OR SOFTWARE DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE USE OF THE SITE IS DONE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK. INVESTINTECH.COM INC. SHALL HAVE NO RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY CONTENT, MATERIALS, INFORMATION OR SOFTWARE.
INVESTINTECH.COM INC. RESERVES THE RIGHT TO MAKE CHANGES OR UPDATES TO THE SITE AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE.
8. Limitation of Liability
IN NO EVENT SHALL INVESTINTECH.COM INC. BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, REVENUE, DATA OR USE, INCURRED BY YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION IN CONTRACT OR TORT, ARISING FROM YOUR ACCESS TO, OR USE OF, THE SITE.
SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY. ACCORDINGLY, SOME OF THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
9. Indemnity
You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Investintech.com Inc., its officers, directors, employees and agents from and against any and all claims, liabilities, damages, losses or expenses, including reasonable attorneys' fees and costs, arising out of or in any way connected with your access to or use of the Site.
10. Privacy Policy
Investintech.com Inc. is concerned about your privacy and will not share information we have collected from you with other companies and organizations for marketing purposes without your consent.
11. Applicable Laws
All matters relating to your access to, and use of, Canadian federal law or the laws of the Province of Ontario shall govern the Site. Any legal action or proceeding relating to your access to, or use of, the Site shall be instituted in a Federal or Provincial court in Toronto, Ontario. You and Investintech.com Inc. agree to submit to the jurisdiction of, and agree that venue is proper in, these courts in any such legal action or proceeding.
12. Copyright/Trademark Information
Copyright © 2000 - 2020, Investintech.com Inc. All rights reserved.
Keep in touch!
This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best possible experience.By continuing you agree to our privacy policy
